for the next steps we are going to need more minerals
single block miners are too much of an hassle
and we can't wait for god to gift us more transceiver
so we will have to ask AE2
we also need some more preparations
and off we go
next, we shall fix some issues with the old assline layout
GregTech pipes did the trick
we will also need an assembly line capable of handling more complex recipes
we can do that using Steve's Factory Manager mod
for example in the normal assline
we can't have recipes that have the same item spread across multiples buses
like the heavy duty plates
moving on, we also have to worry about Lutetium
we are not making enough of it
the main issue is cooling down the water
so let's craft some more turbines
and we don't have to forget to order a new rocket
while AE2 is busy
I think it's a good time for us to touch some grass
in LuV style
so let's make some genetically modified plants
and here we go, a nice plant
in the meanwhile, we also have increased the UU matter and the Lutetium production
we have 32 fluid reactor fueling a GT++ boiler
feeding four XL turbines
and I have lost count of the amount of miners we have
next, we are going to do a little bit more of the mozline
so that we can have some cerium
we need it for the weird alloy
needed for the precision assembler
needed for the neutron activator
needed for the naqudah line
needed for stuff that we will find out
we also need some lithium Chloride
which apparently can only be made by this recipe
so time for some manual LuV work
first we locate some mineral using the LuV tools
next we gather the material
we process it
and finally we void it
that way we can feel the frustration needed to take a break from that game
but don't worry
we will probably get back to it in a few hours
welcome back
as you can see we are low on energy
so let's use this time to see what happened during the break
we have managed to make two precision assemblers
and a fusion reactor
we have also made some improvements here and there
now we just complete the monozite and naquadah line
okay now I think we should make a couple more of fusion reactors mk1 before moving on
one will be dedicated for an early fusion energy production
and one to double the processing speed of AE2
and here we go
this is just a small plant just for sustaining us while we will be working at the bigger versions
as you can see we have now doubled our power production
you might be wondering
what we are going to use all of that power for
but I think the answer is obvious
cobblestone
a lot of cobblestone
and I think we should do some cable management now
like that
I wish we could have used lasers since they sound cool
but we cannot craft them yet
we have now a better farm
and the old one is only 18 TPS
I think it's time to get rid of it
you served us really well, old friend
but it's time to say goodbye
let's do it a bit in vanilla 5 years old style
and a bit in tech it classic style
next we upgrade the ebfs a little bit more
so that we can run out of power
again
if we do not want to give up our cobblestone production
we must increase our power production
right now the best way is to step up our fusion game
let's craft a couple of MK2 reactors
by the way this is netherstar setup
and here we farm shrooms to keep ourselves high
I mean
high on vis
anyways this is for crafting
and this for power production
do you guys know what access to fusion tier 2 means
correct, many things
and the one you thought is probably in the list
let's start by using one of our many assembly lines to craft a armor
since there are a few bugs
and we won't be using many times this recipe
this time we can craft it by hand
we have to manually place each ingredient inside each bus in the correct order
let's do it
and after fixing some charge issues
we finally can fly fast
by the way we now even have one of these cool advanced assembly lines
which can even turn orange
they now do look like proper traffic lights
and after cooking some neutronium
we finally unlocked the UV age
now we rush a UV assembler
and finally, we have access to a proper way of transporting energy
nothing can stop us now
just look at how cool they look
and think about how much power they carry
now as they say
from great power comes great responsibility
so let's gather some materials for the next upgrade of our fusion plant
and this is the best we can do right now
we should probably look into tin plasma though
anyways as you can see from the screen behind me
this is barely enough to make our energy meter measure something
this is not good at all
we need more power
the best route right now is probably
to step further up our fusion tier to unlock better recipes
however, we miserable carbon based life forms can't manage that
we need the help of silicon based life forms
and the only one who can help us create life is
god
we first have to take some bacteria
and seal it inside a petri dish
next we start multiplying this culture into a bacterial vat
we must be careful
and not let this stuff escape the vat
and we shall not eat it
I know that this stuff looks appealing
but just don't eat it
we have to let the population of vat be always at half of the vat space
to maximize its reproduction
and finally, we can use this stuff to make some growth medium
for our stem cells
now we just have to do questionable things to these poor cells
until we get a wetware processor
however a single processor won't be enough
we have to merge many of them to form a single mainframe
however to connect wires and neurons
we need first to do some more research
and apparently, our scanners won't cut it
we have to build a full fledged research station
capable of using the computation power from a quantum computer
and this is the complete setup
we have made a 12 racks computer
for a total of 420 computation
to keep the research time short
we make certain the cat is okay
so that the computer is certain
we place a data stick and the object we want to study in the research station
next we turn on the computer
we have to be careful at how much power it drains
and how much it heats up
and finally we start researching
and here we have our results
we must always remember to turn off the PC
or we will have a high Bill to pay
now we move to the production facility
and put the data in the assembly line
and finally we ask AE2 to start it
next we shall go to new weird planets
visit their oceans and collect some weeds
and do some biological experiments on them to extrapolate extraterrestrial bacteria
next we shall realize that in all of that time
our mega blast furnace has polluted our world a little bit too much
we fought some weird bosses
we increased our power production
we automated some extreme craftings
and crafted an extreme rocket
we fixed the pollution issues by upgrading our mufflers
and upgraded the rating of our blast furnace
we made a few more fusion reactors
and started using our TNT stockpile
we maxed out our power sub-station
and completed our extreme rocket
we built a PCB factory
and we looked up on how to have the materials to make PCBs
and we are getting the last tier of bio-circuit
下面我们需要更多的矿物
单方块矿机太麻烦了
我们等不及上帝给我们更多的超立方体了
所以我们向AE2要一点
我们还需要一些准备
然后，出发
接下来，我们将修复旧装配线布局的一些问题
通过使用GT管道
我们还需要一条能够处理更复杂配方的装配线
我们可以使用SFM来做到这一点
例如，在正常的装配线中
我们不能使用"在不同仓室之间有相同物品"的配方
比如重型装甲板
接下来我们还得担心镥
我们做得还不够
主要问题是冷却水
让我们制造更多的涡轮机
我们不用忘记下单新火箭
在AE2忙的时候
我想现在是我们种菜的好时机
以LuV的风格
所以让我们制造一些转基因植物
欧耶，极品作物
与此同时，我们还增加了UU物质和镥的产量
我们有32个流体反应堆给一台GT++热交换机烧开水
热交换机给四个XL涡轮机产生蒸汽
我已经数不清有多少矿机了
接下来，我们要再做点独居石产线
这样我们就可以得到一些铈
我们需要它来制造奇怪的合金
来做精密组装机
来做中子活化仪
来做硅岩产线
来做我们之后会需要的东西
我们还需要一些氯化锂
这显然只能由这个配方来做
所以是时候进行一些LuV手搓工作了
首先我们用LuV工具找到一些矿物
接下来我们收集材料
处理它
最后销毁它
这样我们就能感受到"让我们暂停游戏去休息"所需的挫败感
不过别担心
我们可能会在几个小时重拾信心
欢迎回来
如你所见，我们电力不足
所以让我们利用这段时间看看休息时发生了什么
我们成功地制造了两台精密组装机
和核聚变反应堆
我们也四处做了一些改进
现在我们刚刚完成了独居石线和硅岩线
好吧，我想我们应该在继续之前再做几个聚变堆mk1
一个将用于早期聚变能源生产
一个给AE2处理速度翻倍
做好了
这只是一个小的工厂，为了在我们制作
更大的聚变堆时，给我们维持电力的
正如你见，我们现在已经将发电量翻了一番
你可能想知道
我们要用这些能量做什么？
但我想答案是显而易见的
圆石
很多圆石
我想我们现在应该整理电线
像这样
我希望能使用激光，因为它们听起来很酷
但我们还不能制造它们
我们现在有一个更好的农场
而旧的只有18 TPS
我想是时候摆脱它了
你已尽职尽责了，老友
但是时候说再见了
让我们用5岁小孩玩MC的风格做一点
用古典科技风做一点
接下来我们升级一下高炉
这样我们就可以又一次
电力短缺
如果我们不想放弃我们的圆石生产
我们必须增加发电量
现在最好的办法是加强核聚变
让我们制作几个MK2反应堆
顺便说一句，这是下界之星的产线
在这里我们种植蘑菇让我们飞起来
我的意思是
vis的量飞起来
不管怎样，这是用来做配方的
这是用来发电的
你们知道有二级核聚变意味着什么吗
对的，很多事情
你在想的那个可能就在其中
让我们选众多装配线中的一条开始制作装备
因为有一些bug
我们不会多次使用这个配方
这次我们可以手动制作
我们必须手动将每个材料
按正确的顺序放入每个仓室中
让我们开始吧
在解决了无线充电问题后
我们终于可以飞得很快了
顺便说一句，我们现在甚至有一条很酷的进阶装配线
它甚至可以变成橙色
它们现在看起来确实像真正的交通灯
在烧了一些中子之后
我们终于解锁了UV电压
现在我们速通一个UV组装机
最后，我们有了合适的运输能源的方法
现在没有什么能阻止我们
看看他们看起来有多酷
想想它们携带了多少能量
现在正如他们所说
能力越大，责任越大
所以让我们为核聚变工厂的下一次升级收集一些材料
这是我们现在能做的最好的了
我们也许应该研究一下锡等离子
不管怎样，正如你从我身后的屏幕上看到的那样
这根本填不满我们的主电网
这一点都不好
我们需要更多能量
现在最好的路线可能是
进一步提升聚变等级来解锁更好的配方
然而，我们可怜的碳基生命形式无法做到这一点
我们需要硅基生命形式的帮助
唯一能帮助我们创造生命的人是
上帝
我们首先得取些细菌
并将其密封在培养皿中
接下来，我们在细菌培养缸中繁殖菌群
我们必须小心
别让这些东西从培养缸里跑出来
我们最好不要吃它
我知道这东西看起来很吸引人
但千万别吃
我们必须让培养缸的输出仓半满
以最大化细菌繁殖
最后，我们可以用它来制造生长培养基
来做干细胞
现在我们只需要对这些可怜的细胞做一些可疑的事情
直到我们得到湿件处理器
然而，单个处理器是不够的
我们得把它们合并成一个单一的主机
然而，要连接电线和神经元
我们首先需要做更多的研究
很明显我们的扫描仪做不到
我们必须建立一个成熟的研究站
能够使用量子计算机的计算能力
这是完成之后的样子
我们做了一台12机架的计算机
总共420算力
以缩短研究耗时
我们确定薛定谔的猫没事
也就是完成未定元解析
我们把闪存和要研究的物品放在研究站里
接下来我们打开计算机
我们必须小心它消耗了多少能量
以及它的热量
最后我们开始研究
这是我们的结果
我们必须永远记得关掉计算机
否则我们的电费账单就要爆炸
现在我们转移到生产设施
并将数据放入装配线
最后我们要求AE2启动它
接下来我们将去新的奇怪星球
参观他们的海洋，收集一些杂草
并对它们做一些生物学实验来提取外星细菌
接下来，我们将意识到在这段时间里
我们的巨高炉对我们的世界造成了太多的污染
我们和一些奇怪的boss战斗
我们增加了发电量
我们自动化了一些梦魇合成
并制作了一个t8火箭
我们通过升级消声仓解决了污染问题
并提升了我们高炉的等级
我们又造了几个聚变堆
并开始消耗TNT库存
我们把能源站升满级
完成了我们的t8火箭
我们建了一个PCB工厂
我们研究了如何获得制造电路板基板的材料
我们就要拿到最后一级生物电路板了
（touch some grass 还有叫人不要沉迷虚拟世界，要去享受现充生活的意思，但这里采用直译）